Ningninghou Then let's scout the area first.
Dingdingdang Yeah, let's do that.
Ningninghou So...
Ningninghou Nan, you take this area, okay?
Nannandu Okay.
Ningninghou This whole area.
Jinjinliang Then I'll take that area.
Ningninghou You take that area.
Dingdingdang I'll...
Kekeai I'll search the dining table area.
Heheda Then I'll take this area.
The countdown begins.
Ningninghou Check that out too.
Dingdingdang Under this table, there's...
Liliwo There's a sound.
Liliwo Intruder!
Dingdingdang Hurry!
Liliwo Someone's here.
Nannandu Where did he pop out from?
Nannandu Don't touch me!
Liliwo What's that sound?
30 seconds deducted.
Ah!
Liliwo What?
Liliwo What the heck is it?
Liliwo Who's there?
Liliwo What is it?
Liliwo That's not a human.
Dingdingdang No.
Dingdingdang Not here.
Liliwo What else is there?
Ah!
Liliwo Who is it?
30 seconds deducted.
Oh my god!
Liliwo It's over.
Liliwo This room is full of people.
Liliwo It's so over.
Liliwo This is terrifying.
Ah!
30 seconds deducted.
Dingdingdang Guys, let's just be bold for once.
Dingdingdang We're definitely failing this round anyway.
Dingdingdang Quick!
Dingdingdang Be bold! Look, quick!
Bro.
Heheda Let's take a one-minute break.
Ningninghou Just now, you guys...
Ningninghou Why did you come over here?
Ningninghou Are you done searching over there?
Nannandu I checked everything over there.
Ningninghou Checked all the boxes and drawers?
Kekeai Nothing around the dining table either.
Nannandu Checked them all.
Dingdingdang At the dining table...
Ningninghou Nothing at the dining table either.
Ningninghou Okay.
Nannandu Nothing.
Ningninghou We don't need to go there, right?
Ningninghou What about the one up there?
Nannandu I looked up there, nothing.
Heheda That candle...
Dingdingdang What about behind the curtains?
Kekeai I checked behind the curtains, nothing.
Ningninghou Okay, let's...
Nannandu The curtains? Those curtains?
Dingdingdang Yes.
Kekeai I looked at that one.
Ningninghou The trash can? These two pots?
Nannandu Nothing.
Ningninghou Checked them all?
Heheda Wait, did you guys not find a single bottle?
Kekeai I found one.
Dingdingdang I have one.
Jinjinliang I don't have any bottles here.
Dingdingdang No bottles by me, at the dining table.
Jinjinliang Come and see.
Jinjinliang I really don't have bottles here.
Ningninghou Okay, how about this.
Ningninghou I suspect someone saw it but isn't saying anything.
Ningninghou So this round, let's...
Dingdingdang Are you serious?
Ningninghou Let's swap areas.
Nannandu Sure.
Ningninghou Sounds good?
Ningninghou Who wants to swap?
Dingdingdang Let me search with you.
Ningninghou Sure.
Dingdingdang I'll go with you.
The countdown begins.
Liliwo Who is it?
Liliwo What the hell keeps making noise here?
Liliwo What the hell?
Liliwo Someone's talking.
Dingdingdang How are we supposed to find it?
Liliwo Okay.
Ningninghou Watch your hand.
Ningninghou What's this?
Heheda I don't know.
Heheda A password.
Dingdingdang 777.
Liliwo That's not right.
Dingdingdang Happy Home.
Liliwo Someone's opening packages.
30 seconds deducted.
Dingdingdang A password.
Dingdingdang Five minutes.
Ah!
I'm going down...
Liliwo I can't do this anymore.
Liliwo Let me rest a bit.
Liliwo This room is a total mess.
Liliwo There are people here, let me rest a bit.
Liliwo People have even entered this room.
Liliwo How can I even rest here?
Liliwo It's full of people.
Liliwo I don't know what they're here to steal.
Dingdingdang Here's a sticky one.
Dingdingdang What is this?
Heheda No.
Heheda It's all this kind of stuff.
The countdown has ended.
Challenge failed.
Please remain where you are.
Wait three minutes for the countdown to restart.
Heheda Found a combination lock.
Heheda A three-digit password.
Kekeai 777.
Ningninghou Happy Road 777.
Dingdingdang I just tried that.
Ningninghou That's wrong?
Nannandu Is it 309?
Ningninghou 309.
Jinjinliang 309.
Ningninghou 309 is wrong.
Dingdingdang Liliwo.
Jinjinliang How many strokes in Liliwo?
Jinjinliang Two, three, four, five, six.
Dingdingdang No, when is Liliwo's birthday?
Dingdingdang Right, Liliwo's grandma is...
Jinjinliang Try 667.
Nannandu His stroke count?
Kekeai I don't think it's outside.
Kekeai It should be inside that combination lock.
Kekeai There's a key.
Kekeai To open that lock.
Kekeai And then it's in there.
Ningninghou What is this thing?
Jinjinliang I know how to solve this.
Ningninghou Subtraction.
Ningninghou 9,999.
Dingdingdang 11,111.
Dingdingdang Minus 999.
Dingdingdang Minus 3,333, then minus 6,666.
Dingdingdang Wait.
Jinjinliang How do we calculate this?
Ningninghou Come on, science student.
Ah!
Dingdingdang No.
Three digits.
Dingdingdang Wait a minute.
Dingdingdang 10,000 minus 9,999 equals one.
Dingdingdang One plus 1,000...
Dingdingdang 1,112 minus...
Dingdingdang 999.
Dingdingdang Equals 113.
113.
Jinjinliang Is it 113?
Ningninghou It's open!
Dingdingdang Yes, it is.
Ningninghou But...
Ningninghou What the heck is this?
Dingdingdang Is Emo here?
Nannandu Should we let him eat? He's sick.
Dingdingdang What the heck is this thing?
Heheda What is it?
Ningninghou After we unlocked it...
Jinjinliang All this effort for what?
Dingdingdang I give up.
Dingdingdang Is it inside the apple?
Jinjinliang Wait, we need to discuss our tactics.
Heheda There's no time.
Kekeai I have no idea anymore.
Ningninghou Did you search those clothes?
Ningninghou Let's go over it again later.
Ningninghou What hasn't been searched?
Jinjinliang He, move that clock and check under it later.
Nannandu Why did you two just see the numbers...
Nannandu Didn't you see the numbers?
Jinjinliang I saw them.
Jinjinliang I didn't have time to process it.
Dingdingdang I just didn't think of it.
Jinjinliang Right.
Ningninghou Okay, it's fine.
Jinjinliang You're suspecting me. You're suspecting me now!
Ningninghou Let's not rush to point fingers right now.
Ningninghou Did anyone search the puppet clothes?
Jinjinliang No.
Kekeai I'll search them.
Ningninghou What about the fridge?
Jinjinliang Searched it.
Kekeai Nothing there.
Heheda Checked everywhere.
Ningninghou Okay, let's confirm this.
Ningninghou Who has searched what so far.
Ningninghou Wherever this key turns up later...
Ningninghou We'll blame the person assigned there.
Ningninghou Sound good?
Dingdingdang I searched here.
The countdown begins.
Dingdingdang I searched there.
Dingdingdang And I searched here too.
Heheda It's starting.
Liliwo Someone's here.
Liliwo Intruder!
Dingdingdang I feel like it's been hidden.
Ningninghou Are you saying someone already found it?
Ningninghou Probably not.
Ningninghou I don't think so.
Ningninghou I believe no one here is that evil.
Liliwo Are you guys helping me move?
Kekeai Where are your things?